Hello, dear viewers.
We are from team chmod 777
from the National Institute
of Engineering.
I am Vachana.
We are discussing on
the problem statement
iTantra from ISRO.
So, it's Indian multilingual TTS
and STT aided neural transceiver
radio access for low bit rate
communication.
What does that actually mean?
Our system, iTantra,
lets two Android devices communicate
even when there is no SIM,
no internet, no router,
connections, nothing.
Our on-device speech-to-text model
takes the speech and converts
the speech into compact text.
The Bluetooth-based transport
and relay layer
will send this text
into another device.
The text-to-speech model will again
convert text into speech,
which is in the message's language.
So, in short,
the speech becomes text
and text is sent
locally, and the text
again becomes speech.